Tell me sir, I keep saying again and again that I don't like something, it is not like that, I like
whatever I like, I say I like it, I do
n't like this, so let me tell you about the long one first,
otherwise Deep will say that you are
giving all the bad ones today, Lombard from IC has
given excellent results, it has a
very strong and good performance on every parameter,
this company of The General Insurance,
186, this will be your stop loss level,
buy the futures for the three targets 1900, 1915 and 193, it is a good
result, a strong result, it is better than expected,
this stock
can show good action today on every parameter, based on this result I
gave the advice to buy, just to make you happy
I am going back to my old track